本字幕由 YYeTs人人影视 原创翻译制作
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新 请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
■
翻译：侯默   淘气   红豆包   Iz   Ｊ小糯
校对：stephanie      时间轴：鱼骨头
■
后期：鱼骨头      总监：stephanie
听好了 给大家打打气
Listen, pep talk.
今天是我们的大日子
Big day today.
我们重... 重...重新开张的一天
It's our grand re-re-re-opening.
是个休息日
It's labor day weekend,
"奇迹码头"里人山人海  所以我们要...
And it looks like wonder wharf is getting mobbed. So we have to...
街道尽头是一家名为"Wonder Wharf"海边休闲娱乐场所
今天也是另外一个大日子
Big day for another reason, too!
琳达  先让我说完
Linda, I'm in the middle of my pep talk.
继续  对不起  继续  继续打你的气
Go ahead, sorry. Go ahead, do your pep.
所以今天我们要卖出一些汉堡
So we have to sell some burgers.
每年的这个周末
every year, this weekend
我们不是走大运就是倒大霉
Makes or breaks us.
谁在放屁
Who's farting?
是吉恩的扬声器
It's Gene's sound effects thing.
听起来是机器人的声音
I thought that made you sound like a robot.
确实能弄出机器人的声音  激光声
It does robot voice, laser sound,
还会放屁声
And fart noise.
天妈啊  听着  我和你们老妈
Oh, god. Listen, your mother and I
要到地下室绞肉
Have to go downstairs and grind the meat.
我们不在  你们这些小孩崽子都知道该做些什么吧
But you kids know where you're supposed to be while we're gone, right?
蒂娜  你负责烧烤架
Tina, you're on the grill.
我的胯裆里刺挠
My crotch is itchy. Oh!
你是以女儿的身份
Ok. Are you telling me as my daughter,
-还是以员工的身份跟我说这话  -以...
-Or as my grill cook? -Um, as...
因为我的员工永远不会跟我说这个
Because my grill cook would never tell me that.
当然  我的女儿
Oh. Also, my daughter
也不该和我讨论类似的问题
Should probably not say anything like that to me.
-问她  问你老妈  -我的胯裆里刺挠
-Tell her. Tell your mom. -My crotch is itchy.
-过来  让我看看  -琳达  不要在这看
- Come here, let me see. - Linda. Not now.
-别啊  让我们都看看  -不行
- No, let's all see it. - No.
我只是不确定
I'm just not sure
是否可以用一只手来烧烤
if I'll be any good on the grill With just one free hand.
我还是先继续说吧
Ok, I'm just going to keep moving here.
露易丝  你负责柜台
Louise, you're working the counter.
我把踏脚凳放在柜台后面
I put your little step stool back here.
但是不要改动黑板上写的东西
But do not alter anything on the chalkboard.
如果我想到一些更好的怎么办
Well, what if I think of something better?
我会忍不住写上去的
Which would be almost impossible not to do.
你想不出更好的
You will not think of something better,
因为"新培根汉堡"是完美的  是最有意思的
Because "new bacon-ings" is perfect. It's hilarious.
对吧  我看  我还是把粉笔拿走
Right? You know what, I'm taking the chalk.
他以为我自己没粉笔
Like I don't have chalk.
吉恩  你负责店外  亲切友善地拿给路人
Gene, you're outside, nicely offering people
-免费试吃  明白吗  -交给我吧
-A free sample, all right? -I'm on it!
但是遇到从隔壁火葬场出来的人
But people coming out of the crematorium next door;
-当然他们情绪很低落  -是啊
- People obviously in mourning... - Yeah?
不要叫他们试吃
Don't offer them samples.
老爸  在外面进入角色时
Dad, when I'm in character out there,
我会很投入的
I get in a zone!
我不能总是留意谁心情悲恸  谁心情不悲恸
I can't keep track of who's in mourning and who isn't.
-总之见到谁拿着骨灰缸  -是啊
- Just anyone with an urn... - Yeah?
别去打扰他们
Leave 'em alone!
我知道  你觉得外面是吉恩的表演天下
I know you think it's the Gene show out there,
但是让人开心和让人心烦之间只有一线之隔
But there's a line between entertaining and annoying.
不是  那纯属想象
No! That's a myth.
好吧  听着  你们是我的孩子  我爱你们
All right, listen. You're my children and I love you.
但是你们在这里的表现却十分糟糕
But you're all terrible at what you do here,
我觉得我应该让你们知道
And I feel like I should tell you,
-如果可以的话  我真的很想炒你们鱿鱼  -鲍勃
- I'd fire all of you if I could. - Bob!
好吧  把手放上
All right, hands in.
别... 蒂娜  你的手就别放上来了
Don't...Tina, don't put your hand in.
-怎么... -好  汉堡大卖
- What... - All right. Sell some burgers!
卖汉堡
Sell some burgers.
鲍勃汉堡
Bob's burgers!
免费试吃
free sample!
来尝尝
Come and get it.
我不太放心让孩子们独自在上面看店这么久
I don't like leaving the kids alone up there for this long.
一定会出事
Something bad's gonna happen.
鲍勃  他们没事  我有个事问你
Bob, they're fine. Please, I asked you a question.
说吧  什么事
Yes, what was the question?
你记不记得我们结婚的那晚
Do you remember our wedding night?
记得  那晚我们在工作
Yes. We worked
因为我们没钱  我记得
'cause we couldn't afford not to. I remember.
你绞得太快了吧  慢些
You know you're grinding too fast. Slow down.
-那天是几号  -几号
- What was the date? - The date?
没错  我们的结婚日
Yes, the date of our wedding!
不记得了
I don't know.
-惨了  是今天吗  -就是今天  鲍勃
- Oh, crap. Is it today? - Yes, bob!
-今天是我们的结婚周年纪念日  -就是今天
- Today's our anniversary. - Yes, it is!
对不起  宝贝  对不起
I'm sorry. Baby, I'm sorry.
我总是忘记重要的日子  你是知道的
I'm not good with dates, you know that.
-今天是你的生日吗  -没错  鲍勃
- Today's your birthday? - Yes, bob!
-今天是我的生日吗  -没错  鲍勃
- Today's my birthday? - Yes, bob!
-今天是临产日吗  -没错  鲍勃
- Your due date was today? - Yes, bob!
顺利吗
How'd it go?
你说呢  好吧  很顺利
How do you think it... good. It went very well.
很好
That's good.
是男孩还是女孩
Boy or girl?
你去哪  我受够了
Where you going? I'm done!
我都道歉了
I said I'm sorry.
鲍勃  我受够了
Bob, I'm done!
琳达  回来  我们要把肉绞完
Linda, come back. We need to finish grinding the hamburger.
天啊  恶心
Oh, my god, gross.
谢谢
Thank you.
免费试吃
free samples.
你不能拿这些让人试吃
Hey, you can't give out those samples.
这些是你刚从地上捡起来的
You just dropped them on the ground.
小声点  你谁啊  专管掉落食物的警察吗
Shh! What are you, the dropping food on the ground police?
-是  -有这么一科
- Yes. - Oh. They have that?
-没错  我是卫生督察员  -什么
- Yes. I'm the health inspector. - The what?
卫生督察员  完毕
health inspector. Off.
-什么  -卫生督察员
- What? - Health inspector!
城市  卫生督察员
汉堡店的天敌
The burger joint's natural enemy.
你好  欢迎来到鲍勃汉堡店
Hello. Welcome to bob's burgers.
今天的特色汉堡是"儿童性骚扰"汉堡
The burger of the day is the child molester.
搭配糖果  明白吗
It comes with candy. Get it?
-明白  -不明白
- Yes. - No.
因为有时候他们会用糖果来
'cause sometimes they use candy
做诱饵
to lure their victims...
是啊  我们明白了
Yes, we get it. Ohh.
这间店是你们父母的吗
Is this your parents' place?
没错  他们在地下室
Yes, they're down in the basement
正在绞肉
Grinding the meat right now. Uh-huh.
不是你们想的那样
That's not a euphemism.
他们真的是在绞肉
They're really grinding the meat.
请让我们看看厨房
Show us the kitchen, please.
我只是想说  我们的结婚纪念日很容易记
I'm just saying, it's easy to remember our anniversary.
9月3号  9/3
It's September third. 9/3.
9可以被3整除
9 is divisible by 3.
什么  那不符合...
What? That's not...
很多数字可以被3整除
A lot of numbers are divisible by 3.
不许和我争辩
Don't argue with me.
好吧  你说的对  9被3整除
All right, you're right, 9 is divisible by 3,
从现在起我会记住
And now I'll remember.
天哪
oh, my god.
你在惹我么
Are you messing with me?
-什么  你是说...  -没错  你就在惹我
- What? What are you... - no. You are.
-我  -你有
- I... - you are!
琳  我忘了  对不起
Lin, I forgot. I am sorry.
我已经说过抱歉了  我会补偿你
I said I'm sorry. And I'm going to make it up to you.
我看到你笑了
I can see you smiling.
我没有笑
I'm not smiling!
你的眼里有笑意
You're smiling with your eyes.
-是什么  -你在干嘛
- What is it? - What are you doing?
-一个聚会  -为什么要这样
- A party?! - Why are you doing this?
楼上有个聚会吗
Is it a party upstairs?!
没有  琳达  你可不可以先把肉绞完
No, Linda, can you please just finish this?
我要上去了
I gotta get back up there.
是去为聚会做准备工作吗
Oh! To get everything ready for the party?
不是  我要去准备做午饭
No! To get everything ready for lunch,
在这个我们要拯救的餐馆里  还记得不
In our restaurant, the one we're trying to save, remember?
去吧  去吧
Go ahead. Go.
好了叫我上去
Call me to come up when it's all ready.
我会表现的很惊讶  就像这样
I'll act surprised, like this...
那是...
That's... ohh!
我心脏都要跳出来了
I almost had a heart attack!
那是惊吓  不是惊喜
That's scared, that's not surprised.
就像自残一样
That's like you hurt yourself.
没错  就这样
Ahhh-ahhh! That's good.
闻闻这个  是不是有股草莓的味道
Smell this. Doesn't it smell like strawberries?
整到了  这是变质的牛奶  傻蛋
Gotcha. It's spoiled milk, dummy.
-你们是卫生督察员  -是的
- So you're the health inspector? - Yes.
我想我得了皮疹之类的皮肤病
'cause I think I have some kind of rash or something.
我不是那种卫生督察员
I'm not that kind of health inspector.
有皮疹症状的烧烤工
Rashy grill cook.
你无法想象
You have no idea
我刚才发生了什么事
What I've just been through.
我的屁股上有没有沾到厕纸
Do I have any toilet paper stuck to my buns?
你们的父母到底在哪里
Where are the grown-ups?!
你一定是鲍勃吧
aha! You must be bob.
你是谁
Uh, who are you?
我们是卫生督察员
We're from the health inspectors office.
我是雨果  这位是我的搭档  罗恩
I'm Hugo, this is my partner Ron.
我是新来的  还没有徽章
I don't have a badge yet. I just started.
快给我
give me that.
拿着吧
Come on!
鲍勃  这是我的检查记录
Bob, this is my violations notebook.
我已经全部写满了
I just filled it.
在你厨房呆了5分钟而已
It took 5 minutes in your kitchen.
-听上去很糟糕  -这是一份记录
- Uh, that sounds bad. - It's a record.
闭嘴
shut up.
更不用说违反童工法了
Not to mention child labor law violations,
违反公共道德
Public decency violations...
公共道德  什么  你们在说什么
Public decency? What...what are you talking about?
"儿童性骚扰"  我想这是个家族餐馆
The child molester? I thought this was a family restaurant.
什么是"儿童性骚扰"
Uh, what's the child molester?
-那是今天的汉堡主题  -不是  不是这个
- It's the burger of the day. - No, it's not.
在有限的私人时间内而已
For a limited time only.
在你上来之前
Till you came back upstairs.
-真有人指使的吗  -有
- Did someone actually order this? - Yeah.
-谁  -他
- Who? - Him.
他看起来像个性骚扰儿童的人
Huh. He looks like a child molester.
露易丝  不要为他服务  让吉恩拿汉堡过去
Louise, don't serve him. Let Gene bring it.
鲍勃
Uh, Bob...
为什么要我去被骚扰呢
Why do I have to get molested?
-因为他不会骚扰你  -为什么
- Because he's not going to molest you. - Why?
因为你重
Because you're heavy.
-鲍勃  -等一下
- Bob - yeah, hold on.
重的孩子也会被性骚扰
Heavy kids can get molested!
是啊  谁会不想去骚扰这张脸呢
Yeah, who wouldn't want to molest this face?
-够了  不是那样  -鲍勃
- That's enough. It's not that. - Bob
我的意思是  吉恩  因为你年纪最大
I mean, Gene, 'cause you're older.
蒂娜才是最大的  让她做好了
Tina's the oldest. Make her do it.
-话到没错  但是蒂娜对付顾客不在行  -鲍勃
- Yeah, but Tina's not good with the customers. - Bob
我对付顾客很在行
I'm good with the customers.
-不是这样  -不是  不是这样
- No. - No. Mmm, not really.
我对付顾客相当在行
I'm great with the customers.
她太孤僻了  帮不上忙
She's autistic, she can't help it.
是啊  我是孤僻了点
Yeah, I'm autistic.
-鲍勃  -再等一会儿
- Bob - just a sec.
不对  你不孤僻  蒂娜
No, you're not autistic, Tina.
地上有几根牙签
How many toothpicks on the ground?
-不要再玩这个游戏了  -来嘛  多少根牙签
- Don't play this game again. - Come on. How many toothpicks?
别玩了  最后只会让我清理牙签
No. It just involves me cleaning up toothpicks.
-一百根吗  -鲍勃
- A hundred? - Bob!
-不对  -一百根吗
- No. - A hundred?
-是三根  -这里有三根牙签
- It's three! - There's three!
-好吧  好吧  现在有几根  -鲍勃
- Ok, ok, how many now? - Bob!
-三根  -不对
- Three. - No!
你真是最孤僻的那种人
Ugh, you're the worst kind of autistic.
-你连数都不会数  -鲍勃
- You can't even count. - Bob!
你想知道我们为什么会在这里吗
You want to know why we're here?
我告诉你  这次不是常规检查
Because I'll tell you, it's not for a routine inspection.
-不是吗  -不是
- It's not? - No.
我们正在调查一起耸人听闻的谣言
We're investigating a very disturbing rumor.
谣言说你的汉堡
There's a rumor you make your burgers
里面有隔壁火葬场里的死人肉
With human remains from the crematorium next door!
我在想这个谣言是怎么传出来的啊
Hmm. I wonder how a rumor like that gets started.
这个汉堡是由我家隔壁的
It's made with human remains
火葬场里的死人肉做出来的
From the crematorium next door.
谁知道呢  孩子们都会说一些疯话
Who knows? Kids say crazy stuff.
这是接下来要发生的
Here's what's gonna happen.
我们要对你们的肉进行检测
We'll test your meat.
如果它含有人肉
If it contains human flesh
或是任何超出食品和药物管理局规定元素的4%的话
Anything above the 4% allowable by the FDA,
你们的餐馆将会被关闭
Then your restaurant will be closed,
而你  先生  也要进监狱
And you, sir, will be going to jail.
这是为我办的聚会吗
Oh, a party for me!
-雨果  -琳达
Oh. Hugo? Linda?
你在这干嘛呢
What are you doing here?
我是卫生稽查员  刚调过来的
I'm the health inspector. I just transferred here.
你在这干什么呢
what are you doing here?
这是我们的餐馆  我们自己的
This is our restaurant. We own it.
你嫁给他了
You're married to him?
你们怎么会认识
How do you two know each other?
我还以为你和鲍勃私奔了呢
I thought you ran off with Bob,
"热点"的餐馆老板
The hot shot restaurateur.
我是啊
I did.
-天啊  -你跟他私奔了
- Oh, god. - You did?
我来
I'm on it.
我可不这么觉得
Yeah, I don't think so!
我真不敢相信
I can't believe...
我不
I can't...
我
I...
我真不敢相信你为了他而离开我
I can't believe you left me for him!
你为了我而离开别人
You left someone for me?
他竟然都不知道
Ugh! He doesn't even know?
我们  我们只是很简单的订了个婚
We were...we were briefly engaged.
我依然记得那天  我听说你们结婚时的情景
I still remember the day I heard you were getting married.
天啊
Oh, my god.
今天是你们的结婚纪念日吗
Is today your anniversary?
是的  你怎么会记得
Yes! How do you remember that?
是9月3日
It's 9-3.
9可以被3整除
9 is divisible by 3.
这是什么狗屁逻辑
That doesn't make sense!
好多数字都可以被3整除
A lot of numbers are divisible by 3.
结婚纪念日快乐
Well, happy anniversary.
这个经营场所正在调查中  食物可能含有人肉
人肉
Human flesh?!
等等  等等  等等  等等
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
这是我们最重要的周末之一
This is one of our biggest weekends.
你不能把这个张贴出去  客人都不会来了
You can't put that up. Nobody will eat here.
挂在显眼的地方
Prominently displayed.
尽管测验好了  伙计  因为全是牛肉
Well, then just do your tests, pal, because it's beef.
抱歉  实验室周一才开门
Sorry! The lab's closed till Monday.
那时才能拿到测试结果
You'll get your test results then.
为你们着想的健康督导
Consider yourself health inspectored!
我  我想试试
I...I'd try it.
等不及了
There's no wait.
你好吗  进来吃个汉堡包吧
Hello, how are you? Come in and have a burger.
非常标准的汉堡
A perfectly normal burger.
城里最正宗的汉堡
Best burger in town.
你们的父亲提过任何
Did your father say anything
-与纪念日有关的礼物吗  -没有
- about an anniversary present? - No.
什么也没有吗  比如在汉堡包里
Nothing? Like maybe hiding a necklace
藏起一串项链
in a hamburger,
或是在水沟下藏一些耳环
or hiding some earrings down the drain,
或类似这种浪漫的事情
or something romantic like that?
这叫浪漫
That's romantic?
是啊
Yeah! Yeah.
你去看过厕所或垃圾桶吗
Did you check the toilet or in the garbage?
吉恩  下来
Gene, get off.
我透不过气来了
You're choking me.
You're choking me!
雨果要把爸爸送进监狱
So is Hugo going to put dad in jail
是因为你甩了他吗
because you dumped him?
不是  雨果要把你爸爸送进监狱
No. Hugo is going to put your father in jail
是因为你姐姐
because your sister
告诉她的同学我们卖人肉
told her class that we serve human flesh.
你为什么要这么做  亲爱的
Now why would you do something like that, honey?
-为什么  -我来告诉你为什么  妈妈
- Why? - I'll tell you why, mom!
安妮塔・瓦斯奎兹的叔叔是西班牙斗牛士
Anita vasquez's uncle is a matador in Spain.
她给大家炫耀她的披肩
She was showing everybody his cape.
我得将风头盖过她
I had to up the ante,
我有什么可炫耀吹嘘的
and what do I have to show for show and tell?
-我什么也没有  妈妈  -冷静
- I got nothing, mom! - Calm down.
-这里没有东西可以炫耀  -露易丝
- There's nothing here to show! - Louise...
-怎么了  -蒂娜 别闹了
- What?! - Tina, stop.
妈妈  你可以向雨果讲清楚让他将告示牌取下来
Mom, you can get Hugo to take down the sign.
我要怎么做
How am I supposed to do that?
他狂热的爱着你
He's madly in love with you.
-动动脑子  女人  -是啊
- Work it, woman. - Yeah.
鞋令足下生辉  华夫饼干上的沙拉三明治
你好
Hello?
琳达
Linda?!
这个周末对我们来说很重要
It's our big weekend.
这个烤肉本应该夹在汉堡中间
I mean, this grill should be covered with burgers right now.
这是给谁做的
Who's that for?
莫特  他打电话订的  他不想在这里被人看到
Mort. He called in his order. He doesn't want to be seen here,
我派吉恩送到火葬场去
so I'm sending Gene over to the crematorium with it.
这样啊
Right.
雨果正在来的路上
So Hugo is coming over.
-要谈谈  和我谈  -什么
- To talk. To me. - What?
别发火  我会说服他
Don't be mad. I think I can talk him out of it,
所有这一切
all of this.
你说"说服他"  是什么意思
And when you say "talk him out of it," what does that mean?
雨果要当我们的新爸爸了吗
Is Hugo going to be our new dad?
-拜托  -只是问问而已
- Oh, please. - Just checking.
也许我应该帮你们制造些气氛
Maybe I should help you set the mood.
点上蜡烛
Put out some candles.
好棒  有蜡烛
Ooh, candles!
晕菜
Ugh, unbelievable.
您的葬礼  您的安息之所  火葬场  你的爱人死了不能当饭吃
鲍勃汉堡外卖
Bob's burgers delivery service!
快进来
Quick!
你为什么和那个人订婚
Why'd you ever get engaged to that guy, anyway?
我那时还年轻  而且我父母喜欢他
Ahh, I was young. And my parents liked him
因为他常做饭
because he always did the dishes.
是啊  我想也是
Yeah, I bet.
而且  他
Ha! Also, he...
他还...
He used to...
什么
What?
他  他碰巧接吻技术高超
He, uh, he happened to be an excellent kisser.
什么  接吻技术高超
What--an excellent kisser?
是  他吻起来非常柔软
Yeah. He was very soft,
而且没有很多的口水
and he didn't have a lot of moisture.
-不像某人  -不像某人
- Like some people. - Like some people?
你觉得我接吻技术很差
You think I'm a bad kisser?
不是
No...
是吗  来亲一个
Oh, yeah, well, how about this?
你在出汗吗
Are you sweating?
没有
Uh, no.
那是我的唾液吗
Is that my saliva?
别发火
Don't be mad!
-不  没有  我一点都不生气  -鲍勃
- Oh, no, I'm not. Not at all! - Bob!
我看我还是走吧
I better go, all right?
我可不想让你沾到我的唾液
I'd hate to get any saliva on you
去找你的完美接吻男友吧
And Mr. Perfect moisture mouth!
我就是唾液分泌旺盛  琳达
I happen to produce a lot of saliva, Linda!
这么说  你成了卫生督察员
So! You're the health inspector, huh?
-那是怎么  -我想为你读读这首诗
- How did that happ... - I want to read you this poem.
"卫生督察员
En. "inspector of health,
情伤督察员"
Inspector of pain." um...
我来到这里  试图寻找尸体
"I came in search of human remains,
我找到了一块人肉
"and I found a piece of human flesh
我原本以为我再也没有机会找回它
I thought I'd never see again
那就是  我的心
-my heart."
很棒
Mm-hmm. Very nice!
雨果  你知道鲍勃不是食人族
Uh, Hugo, you know Bob's not a cannibal, right?
-我不知道  -别这样
I don't know that. Don't do this.
对不起我伤了你的心
I'm sorry I hurt you...
琳达  我可以把你从这一切中拯救出来
Linda! I can save you from all this!
糖果棺材
Wow. A candy coffin.
订制棺材和骨灰盒
Customized caskets and urns,
这是我们的特色
that's our specialty.
那里面躺的是凯弗雷先生
That's Mr. Caffrey
他是凯弗雷太妃糖公司的老板
Of the Caffrey Toffee company.
已经装上升降车了
It's on the lift 'cause they're coming
下午就会有人来取
To pick 'em up this afternoon.
我要再加点调味料
I need more condiments.
别乱碰东西  别乱按按钮
Don't touch anything and don't press any buttons.
您的葬礼  您的安息之所  火葬场
天哪  是鲍勃给我准备的结婚纪念礼物
Oh, my god! It's Bob anniversary present,
他记得
he remembered!
我好激动
This is so exciting.
是一具尸体
It's a dead body!
说不定礼物在下面呢
Maybe the present's underneath.
你现在有麻烦了  女士
You're on a sinking ship, lady.
你最好在事情变得更糟之前赶紧抽身
And you better get off before the ship sinks!
你好  是记者吗
Hello, the media?
热烈祝贺重重重新开业
打倒食人族  制作奶油汉堡  不要"我"做汉堡馅
别吃我  老兄  我不吃肉
大家真是太棒了
Good job, everybody.
惹来一群愤怒的群众
An angry mob,
还就在我们餐馆外面  真是甚合我意
That's just what we wanted outside our restaurant.
他们现在就在那边的小卡车里
They're over there, in their little van,
幸灾乐祸
Inspecting themselves.
人肉还是牛肉?
你觉得我应该把留海往哪边拨
Do you think I should change where I part my hair?
-我看看  -什么事
- Uh, let me see. - Uh, yes?
你能把窗户再开大点吗
Can you open the window a little more?
我又不削你
I'm not going to assault you.
-别碰我  -抱歉
- Don't touch me! - Sorry.
我有点失控了
That just came over me.
听着  我来是想让你和这些人谈一谈
Listen, I came out to ask you to talk to this crowd.
是你招来了这一群愤怒的群众
I mean, you made an angry mob here.
那些是什么东西
Huh. Hey, what's all this stuff?
你们车后面有个化验室
You got a whole chemistry lab back there.
你们不是可以在这里做测验吗
Can't you do the test here,
为什么非得搞砸我的周末
Instead of ruining my weekend?
你没资格对我指指点点
Don't tell me how to do my job.
我可没教你怎么养尸体
I don't tell you how to grow your corpses.
给我过来
Come here.
不  放开我
Aah! No! Let go of me!
去处理那些愤怒的群众吧  祝你好运  鲍勃
Good luck with the angry mob, bob!
我离那车有多远
Uh, how close am I to that car?
要我帮你挪出车位吗
You want me to help you get out of your spot?
好啊  我看不到他车的保险杠  挨得很近吗
Yeah! I can't see his bumper? Am I close?
没事  还有一段距离呢
No, you got room.
倒  倒  停
Keep coming. Keep coming. Stop.
-怎么样  -很近
- How am I doing in front? - It's tight.
往前
Keep comin'.
好  转方向盘
All right, cut the wheel.
-转方向盘  -我在转  我在转了
- Cut the wheel! - I am, I am, I'm cutting it.
你得用力往右转
You gotta cut hard right when you
-出来  我来开  -谢了
- Just get out, I'll do it. - Thank you
城市  卫生督察
我的天哪
Oh, my god.
鲍勃要和人群对质了  我要出去
Bob's confronting the crowd. I'm going out there.
你们呆在这儿
You kids stay inside.
大家静一静
Hey, people!
这太荒谬了
This is crazy.
因为一些私人恩怨  我们被一个反复无常的
We're being smeared by an unstable health inspector
卫生督察员给诬陷了
For personal reasons.
我们都认识大家  大家也认识我们
We know you people, and you know us.
你是修鞋的
You, you're the shoe repair guy.
不  我是锁匠
Nope. Locksmith.
我想说锁匠来着  你是锁匠
I mean the locksmith, the locksmith.
-你还帮我打过钥匙  -那又怎样
- I had keys made by you. - So?
这真神奇  不是吗
That was...Great, right?
有道理
Hmm. Fair.
别  别  别嘘了
No, no, no booing.
别嘘了  莫特
No booing Mort.
你们也认识他的
You know him, too.
他是我们中的一员
He's one of us.
他一直住在这里
This guy has been here forever.
自从我从沼泽港跑出来后
Ever since I got run out of bog harbor.
什么
What?
你为什么要从沼泽港跑出来
Why'd you get run out of bog harbor?
为了给饭店提供人肉
For selling human flesh to the restaurants.
我开玩笑的  朋友们
ha ha, I'm kidding, people!
别当真
Come on.
人人都对死亡这个话题感到不自在
Hey, the subject of death makes us all uncomfortable,
而莫特是个例外
Except Mort.
但是  我们是怎么对待活人的
But what about how we treat the living?
有时候我们对待尸体
'cause sometimes we end up treating those bodies
比对待活人还要友好
Better than we treat these bodies.
我们互相伤害
We break each other's hearts.
我们不记得重要的日子
We forget important dates.
我们在告示牌上写一些伤人的话
We write hurtful things on poster board.
我们以这样的方式对待活人
We mistreat the living
却根本没人在意
and no one seems to care.
而一旦那些人死了
But once that body's dead,
我们却又说  "喂  别虐待尸体"
It's, "hey, don't mistreat the dead body!"
"喂  别吃人肉"
"hey, don't eat the dead body!"
这才是终极罪行吗
That's the ultimate crime, right?
谋杀算什么
Murder, no big deal.
吃人肉  天哪
Cannibal? Whoa!
他是在提倡大家吃人肉吗
Is he defending cannibalism?
-不是  我只是在说...  -食人族
- No, I'm just saying... - cannibal!
-那只是新泽西的一个...  -该死的食人族
- See, that's a new jersey... - Damn cannibal!
朋友们  拜托  我只是想...  别
Folks, please, i'm trying... no.
-食人族  -我不是那个意思
- Cannibals! - That's not what I mean!
他要吃掉我们
He's gonna eat us!
谢天谢地  幸好没碎
Oh, thank god it didn't break.
爸爸  爸爸
Dad, dad!
算了  没什么
Forget it. Never mind.
不  爸  不重要了
Nada. No longer relevant.
他说得对  是吧
He's right, isn't he?
我们就在这间移动实验室检测一下这些肉吧
We can test this meat right here in the mobile lab, can't we?
将肉溶解  再加点酶
We liquefy it, add the enzyme.
如果它变成黄色  说明它有沙门菌
If it's yella, salmonella.
如果它变成绿色  说明它已变了质
If it's chartreuse, it's a deuce,
如果它变成蓝色  那是你的姨妈苏
And if it's blue, it's your aunt Sue.
我知道  罗恩  我知道你在押韵
I know, Ron! I know the rhyme!
难道你以为我不懂韵脚吗
Don't you think I know the rhyme?!
不要紧了  你还不明白吗  他有罪
It doesn't matter. Don't you see, he's guilty.
如果这些肉不是人肉  就是别的什么肉
If it's not human flesh, it's something else.
是脏手巾  是  是别的什么东西
It's dirty hand towels. It's...it's something else!
是他偷了你的女人吗
Stealing your woman?
闭嘴  闭嘴  闭嘴
Shut up, shut up, shut up!
好了  好了  都过去了  都过去了
Oh, ok, that's it, that's it.
发泄出来吧  发泄出来吧
Let it out. Let it out.
你是个失败者
You're a failure.
你真失败  干啥都失败
You failed. You fail at everything.
结个婚也失败
You fail at marriage.
成个家也失败
You fail at family.
你的孩子们也都是败家崽
Your kids are failures.
自己又肥  又没吸引力
And you're fat. You're not attractive.
你吸引过谁啊
You never were.
好吧  年轻的时候  还是有那么点吸引力的吧
Well, you were a little bit, when you were a teenager.
但之后你就发福了
But then you got fat.
他在外面嘀咕什么呢
What is he saying out there?
他在跟餐馆聊天呢  老妈
He's talking to the restaurant, mom.
鲍勃哥  别跟餐馆聊天了  快进来
Bobby, stop talking to the restaurant and come inside.
少烦我
Leave me alone!
鲍勃  快进来
Bob, come inside.
进来  鲍勃  快进来  鲍勃哥
Come on, Bob. Come on, Bobby.
有屁用
What's the use?!
老爸  我是露易丝  你闺女
Dad? This is Louise, your daughter.
是啊  露易丝  什么事
Yes, Louise. What?
我告诉大家伙我们家汉堡
I'm sorry that I told everyone
是用死人肉做的  我很抱歉
That we make burgers from human remains.
好吧  露易丝  谢谢你
ok, Louise. Thank you.
老爸  我是吉恩
Dad, it's Gene.
吉恩  你说吧
Yes, Gene, go ahead.
-老爸  -说啊
- Dad? - Yes!
信号不好  过会儿打给你
I think we have a bad connection. I'll call you back.
-我的老天  -我也想和他说几句话
- Oh, my god. - I want to talk to him, too.
我能听见你说话  只隔了一层玻璃
I can hear you. It's just glass.
我的皮疹现在闻起来有一股熏肉味
Oh. now my rash smells like bacon.
也不刺挠了
And it doesn't itch anymore.
我们会安然无恙的
I think we're going to be ok.
好吧  蒂娜  谢谢你
Ok, Tina, thank you.
老爸  我们的餐馆要倒闭了吗
Dad, is the restaurant going to close?
我不知道  露易丝
I don't know, Louise.
我们就快破产了
We're almost broke.
全市人都以为我们是食人族
The whole town thinks we're cannibals,
我还忘了  我和你母亲的结婚纪念日
And I forgot our anniversary.
琳达  如果你跟了雨果  会幸福很多
You'd have been better off with Hugo, Linda.
-鲍勃  别说了  -不  我是认真的
- Bob, please. - No, it's true.
我连接吻都无法让你满意
I can't even satisfy you with my kisses.
-孩子们  很抱歉  -没关系
- Sorry, kids. - No problem.
多谢分享资讯
Thanks for the info.
我亲爱的鲍勃哥
Oh, bobby!
你给我听好了
Now you listen to me.
虽然你被疑为食人者
I would rather be married
但我宁愿和你这样壮志凌云的人结婚
to a suspected cannibal with a dream like you
也不愿和一个拥有柔软双唇
than a soft-lipped guy
却胸无大志的人在一起
Who never had a dream in the first place.
-你心甘情愿吗  -那还用问
- You would? - No question.
对我和孩子们来说  你就是我们的英雄
You're a hero to your kids and to me.
好了  快进来吧
Now come inside.
进来给我们整点吃的  我们饿了
Come inside And make us some food. We're hungry.
我进去
I'm in.
我这就进去
I'm comin' in.
给我开门  好笑吗  快开门
Open the door. Ha ha. Open the door.
说正经的  给我开门
Seriously, open the door!
孩子们  快让你们的父亲进来好吗
Kids, let your father in the restaurant, please.
让我进去
Let me in!
-你们还卖人肉吗  -不卖
- Still serving human flesh. - No.
-卖  -不卖
- Yes! - No!
我们是"勇于试吃俱乐部"
We have kind of an adventurous eaters club.
我们喜欢品尝新食物
We like to try new things.
你们这里能坐下25个人吗
Can you seat 25 people?
这个嘛  我们也许还有一些人肉
Oh, uh...Well, we might have Some more human meat,
不过一个汉堡要50美元
but it's, uh, $50 a burger.
就这么定了
That's a deal.
好  你说什么  真的  真是太好了
Really... what? Really? Great.
开工吧
let's do it.
欢迎光临
Hello. Welcome.
人肉汉堡  就在屋内
Human flesh right this way.
雨果想把这个给你
Uh, Hugo wanted to give you this.
上面写得很清楚  你们这里绝无人肉...
It states clearly that there was no human flesh in--
别声张  是的  没错  谢谢你  谢了谢了
Shh! Shh. Yes, yes. Thank you. Thanks.
我们加快了检测的速度
We were able to expedite the tests,
检测出100%A等牛肉
And we found 100% grade A beef-- shh, shh!
罗恩  我很抱歉
Ron! I'm just sorry...
-闭嘴  给我闭嘴  -好吧
- Shut up! Shut up. - Ok.
欢迎光临
Hi. Welcome.
琳达  真不敢相信  我们刚才都赚翻了
Linda, I can't believe how much money we just made.
这礼拜一下子就变得美好了
This turned into a great weekend.
是啊  鲍勃  太棒了
Oh, Bob, it's gorgeous.
好像停下来了
Hmm. We seem to have stopped.
鲍勃哥
Bobby!
你一直在练习呀
You've been practicing.
是啊  我上网搜了下秘技
Yeah. I went online, got some tips.
网上还有接吻秘技吗
They have kissing tips online?
我学了几个动作  来试试这个
I learned a few moves. Check this one out.
这是结婚纪念日礼物  送给你
This one is your anniversary gift.
鲍勃哥哥
Oh, bobby!
再猛烈些  鲍勃
Go, Bob!
真难以置信
Ugh, unbelievable.
恶心死我了
Aww, sick!
老妈的手可真不老实
Mom's really handsy.
你们两个贱人
You're a couple of sluts!
我觉得还不错啊
I think it's nice.
快点让这玩意儿转起来
Hey! Get this thing movin'!
坐在这里可真够胆战心惊的了
I'm getting scarred for life up here!